let questions22 = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "to accommodate",
      answer: "C. unterbringen",
      options: [
        "A. verlieren",
        "B. schließen",
        "C. unterbringen",
        "D. werfen"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "circus",
      answer: "A. Zirkus",
      options: [
        "A. Zirkus",
        "B. Fabrik",
        "C. Bahnhof",
        "D. Flughafen"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "to coincide",
      answer: "D. zusammenfallen",
      options: [
        "A. trennen",
        "B. kämpfen",
        "C. fliegen",
        "D. zusammenfallen"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "to commission",
      answer: "B. beauftragen",
      options: [
        "A. spielen",
        "B. beauftragen",
        "C. schwimmen",
        "D. wandern"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "dose",
      answer: "C. Dosis",
      options: [
        "A. Kiste",
        "B. Teller",
        "C. Dosis",
        "D. Korb"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "to dye",
      answer: "A. färben",
      options: [
        "A. färben",
        "B. kochen",
        "C. putzen",
        "D. nähen"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "extent",
      answer: "D. Ausmaß",
      options: [
        "A. Preis",
        "B. Zeit",
        "C. Raum",
        "D. Ausmaß"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "gender",
      answer: "B. Geschlecht",
      options: [
        "A. Alter",
        "B. Geschlecht",
        "C. Größe",
        "D. Gewicht"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "headline",
      answer: "C. Schlagzeile",
      options: [
        "A. Kapitel",
        "B. Notiz",
        "C. Schlagzeile",
        "D. Gedicht"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "informal",
      answer: "A. informell",
      options: [
        "A. informell",
        "B. kompliziert",
        "C. gefährlich",
        "D. präzise"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 11,
      question: "to inquire",
      answer: "D. sich erkundigen",
      options: [
        "A. lachen",
        "B. weinen",
        "C. schlafen",
        "D. sich erkundigen"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 12,
      question: "messenger",
      answer: "B. Bote",
      options: [
        "A. Koch",
        "B. Bote",
        "C. Maler",
        "D. Fahrer"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 13,
      question: "to peer",
      answer: "C. spähen",
      options: [
        "A. tanzen",
        "B. singen",
        "C. spähen",
        "D. laufen"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 14,
      question: "portrait",
      answer: "A. Porträt",
      options: [
        "A. Porträt",
        "B. Teppich",
        "C. Fenster",
        "D. Schrank"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 15,
      question: "to pose",
      answer: "D. posieren",
      options: [
        "A. waschen",
        "B. putzen",
        "C. bügeln",
        "D. posieren"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 16,
      question: "ranch",
      answer: "B. Ranch",
      options: [
        "A. Hotel",
        "B. Ranch",
        "C. Museum",
        "D. Kino"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 17,
      question: "to steer",
      answer: "C. lenken",
      options: [
        "A. drucken",
        "B. malen",
        "C. lenken",
        "D. falten"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 18,
      question: "stripe",
      answer: "A. Streifen",
      options: [
        "A. Streifen",
        "B. Punkt",
        "C. Kreis",
        "D. Würfel"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 19,
      question: "tame",
      answer: "D. zahm",
      options: [
        "A. nass",
        "B. kalt",
        "C. hart",
        "D. zahm"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 20,
      question: "to tempt",
      answer: "B. verlocken",
      options: [
        "A. sparen",
        "B. verlocken",
        "C. sammeln",
        "D. ordnen"
      ]
    }
];

export default questions22;